# Tim Zhlobich

(legal name Tima Jlobitch)

Senior Software Developer

Minsk, Belarus, 220121 (open to relocate)

tim.zhlobich@gmail.com

skype: san\_asm

GitHub

LinkedIn

## **Experience highlights**

7+ years of Scala/Java/full-stack product development

#### Adform (Integrated Advertising Platform), Site Tracking

Adform, Aug 2017 - Jun 2019

Adform is one of top European advertising platforms, it provides Sell Side and Buy Side capabilities to manage ad campaigns and to configure ad serving. The core part in this process is Site Tracking, which allows site administrators to use UI to create and customize scripts that serve ad banners and simultaneously track user activity. Gathered information is used in reports, similar to Google Analytics.

- management tools of user activity tracking
- · end-to-end domain REST & GraphQL services development
- architecture and release planning
- performance analysis

Scala, C#, Java, SQL, MongoDB, Akka, Slick, ASP .NET Core, docker, k8s, JMC

#### wartremover

open source project, May 2016 - present

- Flexible Scala code linting tool (compiler plugin + sbt plugin)
- top 3 contributor
- collaborator

Scala, scalac

#### **Project Falcon**

Kronos Inc. / Epam Systems, Sep 2016 - Aug 2017

- · SaaS tenant management system
- · domain REST service development
- tests

Java, Spring Boot, Postgres, Jenkins

### **Kyriba SaaS**

Kyriba Corp. / Belhard Development, Sep 2012 - Nov 2015

- · proactive treasury management platform
- top 3 contributor
- · full stack dev
  - · requirement analysis, planning
  - DB maintenance
  - business logic
  - UI
  - tests
- organization of a series of internal workshops on ML, distributed systems, text indexing, Scala, Java compilation process

Java, SQL, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Scala, Java EE, Swing, Guava, EclipseLink, JBoss, JUnit, Mockito

## Support level 3

Kyriba Corp. / Belhard Development, Mar 2015 - Nov 2015

- · customer case investigations
- code & performance analysis
- log analysis
- development of log processing tools

Java, SQL, JConsole

### G1 migration project

Kyriba Corp. / Belhard Development, Jul 2013 - Aug 2013

- · benchmark development
- gathering statistics and comparing JVM garbage collectors
- · analyzing G1 weak spots
- preparing migration procedure

Java, JConsole, JVisualVM, GCViewer

#### **Spkr**

open source project, Jan 2016 - Apr 2016

- · asynchronous voice chat
- · full stack dev
- docker-based deployment
- MediaRecorder integration

Scala, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, MongoDB, nginx, docker, Play framework, Apache Kafka, Morphia, Akka, Guice

# Education

no bachelor's degree

## **Belarusian State University**

Applied Mathematics, 2007 - 2010

some university courses

## Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Computer Science, 2011 - 2012

some university courses